'체코, 프라하'
뒷돈 좀 챙기는 건
상관없지만
M doesn't mind you earning
a little money on the side, Dryden.
국가 기밀을
팔면 씁니까
She'd just prefer it
if it wasn't selling secrets.
어설픈 협박
lf the theatrics
are supposed to scare me...
안 통해, "본드"
...you have the wrong man, Bond.
상부에서 나를
제거할 거라면
lf M was so sure that l was bent...
OO요원을 보냈겠지
...she'd have sent a double-O.
지국장쯤 되면
Benefits of being section chief...
요원들 신상 명세는
...l'd know if anyone had been
promoted to double-O status...
훤히 꿰거든
...wouldn't l?
- 암살 전력이 없던데, 최소한...
- 둘!
- Your file shows no kills, and it takes
- Two.
아쉽군
Shame.
친구가 될 수도
있었는데!
We barely got to know each other.
미리 손 좀 썼지
l know where you keep your gun.
이만하면 쓸만하지?
l suppose that's something.
그렇군
True.
어떻게 죽었지?
How did he die?
당신 정보원?
Your contact?
고통스럽게
Not well.
죄책감을 느꼈나?
Made you feel it, did he?
그랬대도
Well...
걱정할 거 없어
...you needn't worry.
두번째는...
The second is
그래
Yes.
거저먹기지
Considerably.
007 카지노 로얄
SUB2SMI & 수정: 슬픈사냥꾼
'제임스 본드 - 007 승격'
'우간다, 음발레'
일면식 없는 자한테
돈을 맡겨라?
So how do l trust this man
that l've never met with my money?
금융 전문가가
필요하대서
You asked for the introduction.
소개했을 뿐이오
That's all my organization
will guarantee.
"화이트"씨한테
이미 들었겠지만
l suppose our friend
Mr. White will have told you...
난 자유투사들의
...that l have provided
reliable banking services...
자산을 굴려왔소
...for many other
freedom fighters over the years.
신을 믿소, "르쉬프"?
Do you believe in God,
Mr. Le Chiffre?
아뇨
No.
투자수익만 믿죠
l believe in
a reasonable rate of return.
안전성이 최우선이오
l want no risk in the portfolio.
물론
Agreed.
전세계 어디서나
인출 가능하고?
And l can access it
anywhere in the world?
그렇소
Yes.
돈을 받았소
"스카이플릿" 주식
l have the money,
so short another million shares...
백만주 공매해요
...of Skyfleet stock.
시장 움직임은
그 반대입니다
Sir, you must know you're betting
against the market.
증권 전문가들은
상승을 예측해요
No one expects this stock
to go anywhere but up.
하라면 해!
Just do it.
'마다가스카'
우리가 찾던 놈이야
얼굴에 화상 자국
Looks like our man.
Burn scars on his face.
폭탄 만들다
데었나 보군
l wonder if bomb-makers
are insured for things like that.
'엘립시스'
움직인다
He's on the move.
날 향해 오고 있어
He's on the move,
and he's heading straight for me.
귀에서 손 떼
Stop touching your ear.
- 뭐?
- 손 내려!
- Sorry?
- Put your hand down.
총 집어넣어
생포해야 돼
Holster the bloody weapon, Carter.
l need him alive.
'남부투 대사관'
'엘립시스'
가끔씩 피눈물을
흘릴 때가
Weeping blood comes merely
from a derangement of the tear duct...
...my dear general.
있지요
Nothing sinister.
별 거 아닙니다
All in.
올인!
l have two pair, and you have
a 17.4 percent chance...
스트레이트가 나와
이기실 확률은
...of making your straight.
고작 17.4%지요
'영국 첩보원
민간인 살해'
"엘립시스" 기한은?
When does Ellipsis expire?
- 36시간쯤, 하지만...
- 아니
- We have less than 36hours. l can
- No. No, no.
무조건 실행한다
That's all the time l have anyway.
손님들 돌려보내
Give our guests
five minutes to leave...
...or throw them overboard.
바다에 던지든가!
Who the hell do they think they are?
지들이 뭔데?
l report to the prime minister,
even he's smart enough...
수상님도 우리 일엔
...not to ask me what we do.
일체 관여치 않는데
Have you ever seen such a bunch
of self-righteous, arse-covering prigs?
불똥 떨어질까봐
몸 사리는 꼴하곤
They don't care what we do, they care
what we get photographed doing.
그깟 기사가
뭔 대수라고
And how the hell
could Bond be so stupid?
"본드"는 제정신이야?
l give him double-O status,
he celebrates by shooting an embassy.
007로 승격하자마자
대사관을 날려?
ls the man deranged?
And where the hell is he?
지금 어딨어?
옛날 같음 적국으로
ln the old days, if an agent
did something embarrassing...
전향해야 했을 거야
...he'd have the good sense
to defect.
냉전 시대가
그립군!
Christ, l miss the Cold War.
'엘립시스 - 추적 중'
'보낸 문자 1개'
'발신지: 바하마'
'오션 클럽'
간덩이가 부었군
You've got a bloody cheek.
죄송해요
Sorry.
다음엔
카메라부터 쏘죠
l'll shoot the camera first next time.
자살하든가!
Or yourself.
치외법권 지역인
You stormed into an embassy.
대사관에 침입해선
You violated the only
absolutely inviolate rule...
외교분쟁을 일으켰어
...of international relationships.
왜?
엄한놈 죽이려고!
And why?
So you could kill a nobody.
생포해 오랬잖아!
We wanted to question him,
not kill him.
머리는 장식이야?
잘 판단했어야지!
For God's sake. You're supposed
to display some kind of judgment.
했어요
l did.
폭탄 제조범이니
죽어도 싸죠
l thought one less bomb-maker
in the world would be good.
그래, 폭탄 제조범!
Exactly. One bomb-maker.
We're trying to find out how an entire
network of terrorist groups is financed...
테러단체 자금줄을
파헤치려고 했는데
피래미 잡겠다고
...and you give us one bomb-maker.
월척을 놓쳤잖아
Hardly the big picture,
wouldn't you say?
조직원도 아닌
용병이었고
The man isn't even a true believer.
He's a gun for hire.
자네 총질 덕분에
And thanks to your trigger finger...
배후 캐내긴
물 건너갔지
...we have no idea
who hired him or why.
우리집은 어떻게
알아냈어?
And how the hell
did you find out where l lived?
본명도 알아낸걸요
The same way
l found out your name.
M이 그런 뜻인진
상상도..
l thought "M" was randomly assigned.
l had no idea it stood for
더 뻥끗하면
내 손에 죽어
Utter one more syllable
and l'll have you killed.
승격은 시기상조였어
l knew it was too early
to promote you.
요원들 수명은
평균보다 짧죠
Well, l understand double-Os
have a very short life-expectancy...
제가 죽으면
실수도 잊혀져요
...so your mistake will be short-lived.
"본드", 자네같은 무대뽀는
이해를 못하겠지만
Bond, this may be too much
for a blunt instrument to understand...
자신감과 자만심은
상극이야
...but arrogance and self-awareness
seldom go hand in hand.
철학자 킬러가 되라?
So you want me to be half monk,
half hit-man?
살인은 쉬워
Any thug can kill.
자만심은 접어두고
l want you to take your ego
out of the equation...
냉철히 판단해서
행동해야지
...and to judge the situation
dispassionately.
자네를 믿었는데
신뢰를 저버렸어
l have to know l can trust you,
and that you know who to trust.
당분간 내 눈에 띄지마
And since l don't know that,
l need you out of my sight.
모래에 머리 처박고
Go and stick your head
in the sand somewhere...
앞날을 고민해봐
...and think about your future.
놈들이 노릴 텐데
Because these bastards
want your head.
지금 심정 같아선
넘겨주고 싶거든
And l'm seriously considering
feeding you to them.
그리고, "본드"
And Bond...
다신 내 집에
몰래 들어오지 마
...don't ever break into
my house again.
그럼...
Ma'am.
'바하마, 나소'
"오션 클럽"에
잘 오셨습니다
Good day, sir,
and welcome to the Ocean Club.
Hey. Hey.
이봐
Hello.
주차 안 시킬 거야?
Are you going to take this
or make me wait?
알겠습니다
죄송합니다
Certainly, sir. Sorry, sir.
Security to car park.
Absolutely incredible.
'7월 6일 녹화'
안녕하세요
체크인?
Welcome to the Ocean Club, sir.
Checking in?
갑자기 오느라
예약을 못했소
Yes. But it's a spur-of-the-moment
thing, and l haven't got a reservation.
아, 네
Okay.
- 빌라 어떠세요?
- 좋소
- We have an ocean-view villa.
- Perfect.
어제 저녁에
Could you do me a favor?
l was here last night...
"애스턴 마틴" 차량
옆에 주차하다가
...and l parked my car next to
a very beautiful 1 964 Aston Martin.
문을 긁어놨는데
차주가?
l nicked the door.
You wouldn't happen to know?
- "드미트리오스"씨
- 그렇군요
- Mr. Dimitrios.
- Right.
그냥 모른 척 하세요
lf he hasn't noticed,
l'm not sure l'd mention it.
워낙 불 같은 분이라
lsn't the type
to take bad news well.
꼭 만나고 싶다면?
But if l felt compelled to find him?
해변가 집이에요
He has a house just up the beach.
고맙소
Thank you.
- 뭐야?
- "본드"가 바하마에 있어요
- What?
- He's in the Bahamas.
그거 알려주려고
이 꼭두새벽에?
You woke me
to share his holiday plans?
국장님 ID로
Well, he's logged into
our secure website...
컴퓨터에 접속했어요
...using your name and password.
비밀번호를
어떻게 알고?
Well, how the hell
does he know these things?
확인 중입니다
Well, l'm doing my best to find out.
- 누굴 살피지?
- "알렉스 드미트리오스"
- Who's he looking at?
- Alex Dimitrios.
인간 말종이지
That slimy bugger.
지금 살펴보는 자는...
Now known associates....
'르쉬프'
"르쉬프"
Le Chiffre.
We've had a good night,
we've had a few drinks.
뭘 드릴까요?
How can l assist you, sir?
소다수 섞은 럼주
Good evening.
Large Mount Gay with soda, please.
- Look what just happened.
- Good job, big boy.
Yeah.
껴도 될까요?
Do you mind if l join?
- Oh, good evening. How are you?
- Good evening.
베팅하세요
Small blind, big blind.
했소
l'm in.
Bet's to you.
행운의 키스라면
2시간 늦었어
lf that was for luck,
you're two hours late.
Two hundred to you.
베팅하실 차례예요
Bet's to you.
알아
l heard you.
Five to call.
- Action's to you.
- Pair of sevens.
Ace high.
체크, 베팅?
Check or bet.
- 체크
- 선생님은?
- Check.
- And to you.
5천!
Five thousand.
5천입니다
Five to call.
- 체크
- 받으시겠어요?
- Check.
- Check to you, sir.
올인!
All in.
잠깐만
No, wait.
2만!
Twenty thousand.
꺼내놓은 것만
가능해요
Table stakes. l'm sorry, sir.
그럼 이건 되겠지?
내 차요, 받겠소?
Okay. This is on the table.
That's my car. Wanna bet?
죄송해요
l'm sorry, Mr. Dimitrios.
잃은 돈 복구할
기회는 줘야잖겠소
Please, no. Give him a chance
to win his money back.
카드 보여주세요
All right, show me, gentlemen.
킹 트리플
Three kings.
There you go with my night.
에이스 트리플
Trip aces.
에이스가
이겼습니다
Aces win.
주차증도!
Oh, and the valet ticket.
고맙소
Thank you.
Sir.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
남편이 쏘아댄
이유 알겠네요
No wonder he was
in such a foul mood.
실수했어요
My mistake.
태워줄까요?
Can l give you a lift home?
그랬단 남편이
미쳐버릴 텐데
That would really send him
over the edge.
너무 잔인하잖아요
l'm afraid l'm not that cruel.
생각하기 나름이죠
Well, perhaps you're just
out of practice.
어쩌면요
Perhaps.
우리집에서 한잔 할래요?
Well, what about
a drink at my place?
당신 집?
Your place?
- 가까워요?
- 무척!
- ls it close?
- Very.
딱 한잔만!
One drink.
다시 오셨군요
Good evening, sir,
and welcome back.
우리집이요
Welcome to my home.
그게 왜 내 잘못이요?
l'm having a hard time seeing
how this is my fault.
사람 필요하대서
연결했을 뿐인데
lt's your plan.
All l did was get you the man.
영국 첩보국의
감시를 받고 있었어
A man who was under surveillance
by the British Secret Service.
이젠 자넬 못 믿겠군
Which makes me wonder
if l can trust you at all.
그건 상관없지만
Then don't. l couldn't care less.
체면 구기곤
못 살지
But l do care about my reputation.
딴 놈을 대주겠소
l have someone else
willing to do the job.
임무 알려주고
He just needs the particulars...
돈만 주쇼
...and payment.
유부녀를 좋아해요
"제임스"?
You like married women,
don't you, James?
부담이 없잖소
lt keeps things simple.
악동들이란 정말!
What is it about bad men?
당신, 남편...
You, my husband....
착한 남자들도
l had so many chances
to be happy...
숱하게 많은데
...so many nice guys.
왜 하나같이
당신 같질 않을까?
Why can't nice guys
be more like you?
나랑 같다면
악동일 테지
Well, because then they'd be bad.
Yes.
악동이 더 짜릿해!
But so much more interesting.
남편이 악동인
이유가?
What makes your husband
a bad man?
천성이 그래요
His nature, l suppose.
하는 일도?
The nature of his work?
무슨 일을 하는진
나도 몰라요
A mystery, l'm afraid.
그이한테 접근하려고
날 유혹한 거군요
l'm also afraid you will sleep with me
in order to get to him.
두렵소?
How afraid?
아니, 전혀!
Not enough to stop.
사적인 질문
괜찮겠소?
Can l ask you a personal question?
곧 바빠질 테니
빨리 물어봐요
Now would seem
an appropriate time.
"엘립시스"라고
들어봤소?
Does "ellipsis"
mean anything to you?
물어볼까요?
Should l ask him about it?
나중에!
Perhaps later.
여보?
Yes, dear?
l'm on the last flight
tonight to Miami.
Don't wait up.
l'll be back in the morning.
알았어, 이해해
Okay, l understand.
내일 봐
See you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
마이애미 행
비행기를 탄다니까
Apparently he's on
the last flight to Miami...
밤새도록 날
심문할 수 있겠네요
...so you have all night
to question me.
그렇담
l n that case...
샴페인이
...we're gonna need...
더 필요하겠군
...some more champagne.
Good evening. Room Service.
프랑스산 볼링거
샴페인 부탁해요
Good evening. Can l get a bottle
of chilled Bollinger Grand Ann챕e...
철갑상어 캐비아도
...and the beluga caviar?
소스 곁들여서
- With everything?
- Yes, with everything.
- And would that be for two, sir?
- What?
네?
- For two?
- No, for one.
아니, 1인분만!
'인체의 신비'
기다려요
Wait here.
53번이요
There you go. Number 53.
Dr. von Hagens' Body Worlds
invites visitors...
...to observe the body's various
locomotive,, digestive...
...nervous and vascular systems.
Please may l have your attention,
ladies and gentlemen?
l believe it is something very special,
what we see here.
This is edutainment.
'보낸 문자 - 엘립시스'
fixed in dramatic
and athletic poses...
...that reveal the true-to-life spatial
relationships amongst organs.
여보세요?
Hello.
Do not leave your vehicle unattended.
Welcome to Miami
l nternational Airport.
Curbside parking in front
of the terminal is restricted....
- Yes.
- lt's Bond. l need her now.
"본드"야, M 바꿔
지금 바쁘시니
메시지 남겨요
l'm afraid she can't be disturbed.
Can l take a message?
마이애미 공항 측에
폭탄 테러 가능성을
Listen, you go and find her, tell her
to call Security at Miami Airport...
경고하라고 전해
지금 당장!
...because l think a bomb is about
to go off. Do it now.
- 연결할게요
- 진작에!
- Sorry, can l put you on hold?
- l thought you might.
"본드", 대체 무슨
꿍꿍이야?
Bond? What the hell are you up to?
다시 걸죠
l'll call you back.
'엘립시스'
"스카이플릿"사
신형 항공기
- The Skyfleet S57O prototype.
- What about it?
마이애미 공항에서
처음으로 공개돼요
"The largest airplane in the world will
be unveiled today at Miami Airport. "
Oh, my God !
"본드"?
"본드"!
Bond? Bond!
"스카이플릿"항공기가
H is target is the Skyfleet prototype.
놈의 타겟이야
lt's launching today.
끊을게요
l gotta go.
Stop ! Stop !
전부 피해요!
빨리!
Get moving !
Let's go, let's go, let's go !
공매한 주식값이 올라
손실이 막대합니다
The puts expired. l'm sorry,
l'm not sure yet how much you've lost.
정확히 1억 120만
6천불이지
One hundred and one million,
two hundred and six thousand dollars.
쥐새끼가 있다
Someone talked.
- You got everything you need?
- Yeah, l have.
l'm gonna get a few more photos....
시체를 몰고 다니는군
Quite the body count
you're stacking up.
고문을 당했어
남편이 죽었으니
She was tortured first.
As you'd already killed her husband...
여자를 족친 거지
...she must have been
the only one left to question.
신분 노출했어?
Did she know anything
that could compromise you?
아뇨
No.
- 이름이나 타겟은?
- 아뇨!
- Not your name, what you were after?
- No.
"드미트리오스"는
Dimitrios worked as a middleman.
무기, 용병을 대는
Knew where to put his hands
on weapons...
공급책이었어
...and people who could use them.
지난 수년간
He worked with anyone
who had money.
"르쉬프"란 자와
함께 일해왔는데
For years he was involved with a man
we knew as Le Chiffre...
테러 조직의
...a private banker
to the world's terrorists.
돈을 굴려주는
금융 전문가야
He invested their money, gave them
access to it wherever they wanted.
때맞춰 왔군
Oh, good. You're here.
알바니아 출신
체스 챔피언에
Albanian, we believe.
Chess prodigy.
포커에 미쳐있는
수학 천재지
A bit of a mathematical genius
and liked to prove it by playing poker.
절 감시하시겠다?
So you can keep an eye on me?
그래
Yes.
9/11사태 직전
항공사 주식이
When they analyzed
the stock market after 9/11...
대량 공매됐고
주가가 폭락해
...the ClA discovered a massive
shorting of airline stocks.
누군가 일확천금을
벌어들였어
When the stocks hit bottom on 9/12,
somebody made a fortune.
이번 일도 유사해
The same thing happened
this morning with Skyfleet stock...
다만 테러 불발로
...or was supposed to.
"스카이플릿"사는
파산 면했지만
With their prototype destroyed, the
company would be near bankruptcy.
누군간 1억불 이상
손해봤지
l nstead, somebody lost over
$1OO million betting the wrong way.
"르쉬프" 소행이다?
You think it's this man Le Chiffre.
몬테네그로
카지노 로얄에서
Which would explain how he could
set up a high-stakes poker game...
포커 게임을 한단 첩보야
...at Casino Royale in Montenegro.
참가자는 10명, 최소 참가비는
두당 1천 5백만
Ten players, $1O million buy-in,
5 million re-buy.
전부 딴다면
1억 5천만 불이지
Winner takes all.
Potentially 15O million.
놈을 찾아내는
수고는 덜었군요
Good.
Then we'll know where he'll be.
깨끗이 처리할까요?
아님 경고만?
Do you want a clean kill
or to send a message?
죽으면 쓸모 없어
놈한텐 그런 거액이 없어
We want him alive. Le Chiffre
doesn't have 1OO million to lose.
주식으로 날린
고객들 돈을
Has he been playing the stock market
with his clients' funds?
포커로 메꿀
속셈이군요
They're not gonna be too happy
when they find out it's gone.
막아야 돼
We can't let him win this game.
빈털터리 만들어서
lf he loses,
he'll have nowhere to run.
신변보호를 대가로
정보를 얻어내야지
We'll give him sanctuary
in return for everything he knows.
자넬 그 포커 판에
l'm putting you in the game...
대타로 넣어주겠어
...replacing someone
who's playing for a syndicate.
포커에 일가견 있다고
들었거든
According to Villiers,
you're the best player in the Service.
내키진 않지만!
Trust me, l wish it wasn't the case.
사심을 버리라고
충고해봐야
l would ask you if you could remain
emotionally detached...
씨알도 안 먹히겠지?
...but l don't think
that's your problem, is it, Bond?
절대!
No.
보고는 생략해
Don't worry about keeping in touch.
위치 파악되니까
We'll know where you are.
손 떼래도
You can stop pretending.
포기 안할 거란 거
알았죠?
You knew l wouldn't let this drop,
didn't you?
그게 자네잖아
Well, l knew you were you.
'몬테네그로'
Thank you.
내가 돈이에요
l'm the money.
돈보다 낫군
Every penny of it.
재무부에서 자금을
대기로 결정했어요
The Treasury has agreed
to stake you in the game.
"베스퍼"?
"Vesper. "
부모 원망 좀 했겠군
Well, l do hope you gave
your parents hell for that.
Thank you.
상관 수완이
좋은가 봐요
Your boss must be well-connected.
일사천리로
결정 되더군요
l've never seen so much
go out the door so quickly.
꽤 세련됐어
Or quite so stylishly.
돈은 어딨소?
May l ask you where it is?
천만은 계좌로
입금됐고
Ten million was wired
to your account in Montenegro...
5백만은 상황 봐서
내가 결정해요
...with a contingency for 5 more
if l deem it a prudent investment.
잃으면 정부가
테러 군자금을
l suppose you've given some thought
to the notion that if you lose...
대준 꼴 된다는 거
알죠?
...our government
will have directly financed terrorism.
뭐가 맛있죠?
What looks good?
이긴단 보장은 없다?
So you're telling me it's a matter
of probability and odds.
슬슬 걱정되네요
l was worried there was
some chance involved.
최고의 패를 가져도
질 수가 있지
Well, only if you assume the player
with the best hand wins.
"블러핑" 때문에?
So that would be
what you call "bluffing"?
들어봤군
You've heard the term.
그렇담 심리전의
중요성을
Then you'll also know that in poker
you never play your hand.
알겠군
You play the man across from you.
- 사람 심리, 잘 읽어요?
- 물론
- And you're good at reading people?
- Yes, l am.
당신 목소리에선
Which is why
l've been able to detect...
냉소를 감지했지
...an undercurrent
of sarcasm in your voice.
미덥지를 않아서요
l'm now assured our money
is in good hands.
우리 계획을
안 믿는군
You don't think
this is a very good plan, do you?
있긴 해요?
So there is a plan?
엄청난 돈과
목숨을 걸곤
l got the impression
we were risking millions of dollars...
요행수 바라는
꼴이잖아요
...and hundreds of lives
on a game of luck.
할 말 있어요, "본드"?
What else can you surmise,
Mr. Bond?
당신에 대해?
About you, Miss Lynd?
예쁜 외모가
Well, your beauty's a problem.
일에 방해된다고
걱정이지
You worry you won't
be taken seriously.
똑똑하고 예쁘장한
여자들은 다 그렇죠
Which one can say of any
attractive woman with half a brain.
그렇긴 해도
True, but this one
overcompensates...
남자처럼 차려 입고
...by wearing
slightly masculine clothing...
누구보다도 열심이지만
...being more aggressive
than her female colleagues...
그런 의욕적인
태도가
...which gives her a somewhat
prickly demeanor...
까칠한 여자라는
인상을 심어줬고
...and ironically enough, makes it
less likely for her to be accepted...
남자 상관들
눈밖에 나서
...and promoted
by her male superiors...
승진은 꿈도 못 꾸지
...who mistake her insecurities
for arrogance.
평소라면 외동딸로
생각하겠지만
Now, l'd have normally
gone with only child...
부모 얘길 꺼내도
대꾸 않는 걸 봐선
...but, you see, by the way you ignored
the quip about your parents...
고아인 게 틀림없어
...l'm gonna have to go with orphan.
좋아요
All right.
옥스퍼드 출신들만
By the cut of your suit,
you went to Oxford or wherever...
입을만한 양복 입고
...and actually think
human beings dress like that.
거드름 피우지만
But you wear it with such disdain...
부잣집 도련님하곤
...my guess is
you didn't come from money...
거리가 먼 것 같네요
...and your school friends
never let you forget it.
고학생으로 자라서
Which means you were
at that school by the grace...
매사에 호전적이고
...of someone else's charity,
hence the chip on your shoulder.
날 고아로 생각한 건
And since your first thought about me
ran to orphan...
자신이 고아라서겠죠
...that's what l'd say you are.
진짜군요
Oh, you are.
"블러핑"?
맘에 들어요
l like this poker thing.
여왕님과 조국을
And that makes perfect sense...
수호하려면
...since M l6 looks
for maladjusted young men...
당신같이 막나가는
...that give little thought
to sacrificing others...
사람도 필요할 테죠
...in order to protect
Queen and country.
옛날 요원들은
You know...
살인 미소와 명품 시계가
트레이드 마크였죠
...former SAS types with easy smiles
and expensive watches.
- 롤렉스?
- 오메가!
- Rolex?
- Omega.
멋지네요
Beautiful.
초면에
Now, having just met you...
냉혈한이라
단정짓진 않겠어요
...l wouldn't go as far as calling you
a cold-hearted bastard.
고맙군
No, of course not.
그치만 당신한텐
여자가
But it wouldn't be a stretch
to imagine.
삶의 동반자가 아닌
You think of women
as disposable pleasures...
쾌락의 대상이겠죠
...rather than meaningful pursuits.
매력 있다는 건
인정하지만
So as charming as you are,
Mr. Bond...
돈을 지켜보겠어요
...l will be keeping my eye
on our government's money...
당신의 완벽한
히프도!
...and off your perfectly formed arse.
눈썰미 있군
You noticed?
회계사도
상상력은 있죠
Even accountants have imagination.
스테이크 어땠어요?
How was your lamb?
꼬치였소
Skewered.
최고였지
One sympathizes.
굿이브닝, "본드"씨
Good evening, Mr. Bond.
굿이브닝, "린드"양
Good evening, Miss Lynd.
스플렌디드
호텔입니다
- Hotel Splendid, sir?
- That's right.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
지시 사항이오
lt's just last-minute details.
우리가 연인이군
Apparently we're very much in love.
그런 지시 사항을
포터가 알려줘요?
Do you usually leave it to porters
to tell you this sort of thing?
금방 끝날
로맨스일 경우만!
Only when the romance
has been necessarily brief.
난 "알링턴 비치"
전문 도박사고
l'm Mr. Arlington Beech,
professional gambler...
당신은 왕가슴...
...and you're
Miss Stephanie Broadchest
- 거짓말!
- 그렇게 적혔소
- l am not.
- You're gonna have to trust me on this.
못 믿어요
Oh, no, l don't.
오래된 연인이니
We've been involved
for quite a while...
스위트룸을 같이
쓰라는군
...hence the shared suite.
부모님이 독실한
가톨릭 신자라서
But my family
is strict Roman Catholic...
방 2개짜리로!
...so for appearances' sake,
it'll be a two-bedroom suite.
연인한테 종교는
큰 문젠데!
l do hate it when religion
comes between us.
밤엔 방문 잠그고!
Religion and a securely locked door.
걱정 안 해도 되죠?
Am l going to have a problem
with you, Bond?
걱정 마요
당신, 내 스타일 아냐
No, don't worry. You're not my type.
똑똑해서?
Smart?
미혼이라!
Single.
어서 오세요
성함이?
Welcome to the Hotel Splendid.
Your name, sir?
"제임스 본드",
"비치"로 예약돼있소
James Bond. You'll find
the reservation under Beech.
- 환영합니다
- 서명해요
- Welcome, Mr. Bond.
- You sign that, dear.
재무부 회계사잖소
You represent the Treasury.
편히 지내세요
Thank you. Enjoy your stay.
그러리다, 고맙소
l will. Thank you.
웃기네요
Very funny.
"르쉬프"는
인맥이 막강해요
Look, if Le Chiffre
is that well-connected...
내 정체를 알면서
...he knows who l am
and where the money's from.
게임에 넣어줬소
Which means he's decided
to play me anyway.
절박하거나
지나친 자신감이지
So he's either desperate
or he's overly confident...
둘 중 하나일 텐데
...but either way, that tells me
something about him.
굳이 숨길 거 없잖소
And all he gets in return
is a name he already has.
그도 당신을
파악했겠죠
And now he knows
something about you.
무모하단 거!
He knows you're reckless.
따로 타요
Take the next one.
당신 자만심이 탈
공간이 없네요
There isn't enough room for me
and your ego.
"본드"씨?
Mr. Bond?
- 소포가 왔어요
- 고맙소
- lt was left for you.
- Thank you.
나도 사랑해요, M
l love you too, M.
"르네 매티스"일세
자네들 접선책이지
My name is Mathis. Rene Mathis.
l'm your contact here.
놈이 눈치챘어요?
Does he know
we've been watching him?
"르쉬프"?
아닐 거야
Le Chiffre? l don't think so.
내가 미행했단 걸
알지는 모르겠군
Probably because there's no "we. "
J ust me.
여기선 사고 쳐도
l'm afraid if you get
into trouble here...
지원 병력 기대 마
...the cavalry won't be
coming over the nearest hill.
어제 도착해선
Le Chiffre arrived yesterday...
힘있는 인사들을
만나고 다니더군
...and spent the time reestablishing
old relationships.
경찰 국장하고
돈독한 사이지
The chief of police and he
are now quite close.
콧수염 기른 남자
That's him, with the mustache.
내 왼쪽 뒤로
Over my left shoulder.
그놈과 섞이면
삶이 힘들겠군
Well, that could make life
quite difficult.
명도 짧아지겠지
Yeah, and quite possibly shorter.
치밀하질 못한
사람이라
He's not a very subtle man.
내가 매수하려고
애써봤는데
l thought about trying to buy
his services, but we frankly...
"르쉬프"한테 밀렸어
...couldn't afford to outbid Le Chiffre.
요즘 MI6는
l hate to say it...
회계사들이 쥐고
흔드는가 보더군
...but the accountants seem
to be running Ml6 these days.
회계사한테
개인적 감정은 없소
Oh, not that l have anything
against accountants.
대부분은
좋은 사람들이죠
Many of them are lovely people.
그래서 부국장한테
국장이 돈 받은
So l decided that it was cheaper
to supply his deputy...
결정적인 증거를
제공했지
...with evidence
that we were bribing the chief.
그 포토샵이란 거
쓸모가 참 많더군
lt's amazing what you can do with
Photoshop these days, isn't it?
성공 확률이 높아졌어
"본드"
l think your odds are improving,
Mr. Bond.
네?
Yes?
당신 거요
For you.
그걸 입어라?
Something you expect me to wear?
우아한 자태로
l need you looking fabulous.
내 목에 키스해야
So when you walk up behind me
and kiss me on the neck...
사람들이 당신한테
...the players will be thinking
about your neckline...
한눈 팔 거 아뇨
...and not about their cards.
그럴 수 있겠소?
Do you think you can
do that for me?
노력해보죠
l'll do my best.
고맙소
Thank you.
이 재킷은 뭐요?
l have a dinner jacket.
당신이 고른 건
너무 평범해서
There are dinner jackets
and dinner jackets.
그걸 입어요
This is the latter.
갑부처럼 보여야
의심을 안 받죠
And l need you looking like a man
who belongs at that table.
어떻게...
How?
맞춤이잖소
lt's tailored.
눈대중으로 치수 쟀어요
l sized you up the moment we met.
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening.
Thank you.
선생이 대타시군요
And you must be
Mr. Bliss' replacement.
반갑소, "비치"씨
Welcome, Mr. Beech.
아님 "본드"인가?
좀 헷갈려서
Or is that Bond?
l'm a little confused.
헷갈리면 안되죠
Well, we wouldn't want that,
would we?
여러분, 환영합니다
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
종목은
홀뎀 포커이고
As you know, the game is no-limit
hold 'em poker.
베팅 금액은
무제한
Five communal cards,
two in the hole.
스위스 은행에서 오신
Monsieur Mendel here represents
the Basel Bank, Switzerland...
"멘델"씨입니다
...holding the stakes.
모두 천만달러씩
예치하셨고
You have each deposited
$1O million buy-in.
5백만 추가가
가능합니다
A further buy-in of 5 million
can be made by electronic transfer.
게임이 끝난 뒤
The money will remain in escrow
until l return...
승자가 비밀번호를
...and the winner of the contest
enters his or her password...
입력하면
...into the encryptor...
그 즉시 전액이
...whereupon the entire sum
will be wired...
지정하신 계좌로
이체됩니다
...to any bank account
in the world you nominate.
"본드"씨?
Mr. Bond?
비밀번호를 정해
입력해주세요
We proceed alphabetically.
Please be so kind as to enter
a password of your choice.
최소한 6자리요
Six letters or more.
순서를 정하겠습니다
H igh card for dealer position.
"갈라도"씨
lt's Signor Gallardo.
"카미노프스키"씨
기본 베팅 5천
Mr. Kaminofsky is
the small blind, $5,OOO...
후쿠투"씨는
1만을 베팅합니다
...and Mr. Fukutu, the big blind,
$1O,OOO.
행운을 빕니다
Well, enjoy the game.
플레이어 넷
Four players.
베팅하세요
lt's your bet.
체크
Check.
5만 베팅
Bet. Fifty thousand.
콜
Call.
폴드
Fold.
2명 남았습니다
Fold. Heads up.
"르쉬프"씨
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
10만 베팅
Bet. One hundred thousand.
사람들이 볼 때
들어오기로 했잖아?
Weren't you supposed to enter
so the others could see you?
그래요?
미안해요
Was l? Forgive me.
행운을 빌어요
Good luck, darling.
lt's up to you, Monsieur Bond.
베팅하세요, "본드"씨
"본드"씨?
Monsieur Bond?
베팅액이 얼마요?
10만?
Oh, l'm sorry. What was the bet?
A hundred thousand?
콜
Call.
Hello.
얼마나 아름다운진
말할 필요가 없겠죠?
l suppose l don't have to tell you
how beautiful you look.
사람들 시선을
확 사로잡았어요
Half the people at that table
are still watching you.
샴페인
Champagne.
"르쉬프"씨
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
20만 베팅
Bet. Two hundred thousand.
상대가 받았습니다
카드를 보여주시죠
Monsieur, you have been called.
Showdown, please.
풀하우스입니다
9 석장과 2 두장
A full house to Monsieur Le Chiffre.
Deuces full of nines.
"본드"씨?
Mr. Bond?
폴드
Fold.
바텐더 좀?
Send the barman over, please.
드라이 마티니
잠깐만
A dry martini. Wait.
진, 보드카
Three measures Gordon's,
one of vodka...
백포도주
섞어서 흔들고
...half of Kina Lillet,
shake it over ice...
- 얇은 레몬 껍질 넣고
- 네
-...then add a thin slice of lemon peel.
- Yes, sir.
- 나도 같은 걸로!
- 나도
- You know, l'll have one of those.
- So will l.
알겠습니다
Certainly.
나도 그걸로 한잔
레몬은 빼고
My friend, bring me one as well.
Keep the fruit.
끝났소?
That's it?
포커 계속할까요?
Anyone want to play poker now?
급하시군
Someone's in a hurry.
실례하겠소
Would you excuse me?
달콤하군
You taste nice.
위장 노출됐잖아요
- l thought we dispensed with covers.
- No.
가짜 연인이란 게
들통난 건 아니지
We dispensed with one that was
of no use and created another that is.
- 놈이 봐요?
- 그래
- ls he watching?
- Yes.
잘됐군
Good.
지금처럼 계속 잃다간
This is me in character pissed off
because you're losing so fast...
자정도 못 넘기겠어요
...we won't be here past midnight.
그랬단 알아서 해요
Oddly, my character's feelings
mirror my own.
Check.
맛이 괜찮은걸
- You know, that's not half bad.
- Up to you.
이름을 지어야겠군
l'm gonna have to think up
a name for that.
습관을 알아보려고
져준 거요
lt was worth it to discover his tell.
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
"블러핑"할 때
움찔대요
The twitch he has to hide
when he bluffs.
- 풀하우스였잖아요
- 마지막 카드 덕분에
- Bluffs? He had the best hand.
- Which he got on the last card.
그림이 그려진 거요
The odds against were 23-to- 1,
and he'd know that.
이번에 이긴 건
When he did his first raise
he had nothing.
순전히 운이지
Winning was blind luck.
도청 장치는?
- Did you get the bug?
- Yes.
Bet. One hundred thousand.
Thank you.
lt's your play, Monsieur Fukutu.
진짜 이길지도
모르겠소
Maybe he can actually pull this off.
Call.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
게임을 시작한 지
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mesdames, Messieurs...
4시간 됐습니다
...we've now been
playing for four hours.
1시간 휴식 취하고
계속하겠습니다
lt's time for a short break.
We will resume play in one hour.
난 오늘 저녁 일을
상부에 보고해야겠어
Well, l think l'll report
on the evening's frivolities.
어때요?
So?
뭘 하고 싶다구?
You want to do what to me?
무슨 소리예요?
You've lost me completely.
방에서 할 게 있다며,
그럼 가자구
You just said you can't wait
to get me back to the room. Come on.
급한 일이란 게
뭐야?
So, what's so damn important?
미안해요
l'm sorry.
내 돈 어딨어?
Where is my money?
- Good evening.
나한테 온 물건이
있을 텐데?
You're holding a parcel for me.
고맙소
Thank you.
내 돈을 날려놓고
무사할 줄 알았어?
Do you think you can lose that kind
of money and no one would notice?
돈은 그대로요
Your money is safe.
뜯어봐요
Open that.
내일 주겠소
You'll have it tomorrow.
전부 다!
All of it.
손을 자르고 싶지만
그럼 카드를 못하지
l would take a hand for this betrayal,
but you need it to play cards.
팔 내밀어
Hold out your arm.
팔을 안 내밀면
Hold out your arm, my beauty...
목이 날아가
...or l will take your head.
방에서 기다려요
Go to the room. Wait for me there.
계단으로!
Stairs.
말릴 생각을 않는군
Not a word of protest.
새 애인 찾아봐
You should find a new boyfriend.
"매티스" 찾아서
Go find Mathis.
이 시체들
처리하라고 해요
Tell him l've hidden the bodies here
and l want him to get rid of them.
빨리 가요
가!
Do that now. Go. Go, go !
셔츠가 바뀌었군요
You changed your shirt, Mr. Bond.
푼돈 잃곤
진땀 좀 흘리셨나?
l hope our little game
isn't causing you to perspire.
약간
A little.
그치만 피눈물보단
진땀이 낫겠죠
But l won't consider myself to be
in trouble until l start weeping blood.
전부 오셨으니
게임 계속하죠
Ladies and gentlemen, if everybody's
ready, let's continue the game.
손가락에 묻은 피가
씻기질 않아요
lt's like there's blood on my hands.
lt's not coming off.
보여줘요
Here, let's see.
이제 됐소
That's better.
추워요?
You cold?
Yeah.
Here.
시체 처리는?
You have any trouble
with the bodies?
별 거 아녔어
Less than some.
죽은 시체도
때론 쓸모가 많지
Being dead doesn't mean
one can't still be helpful.
놈을 초조하게
만들어야겠어요
That'll keep Le Chiffre
looking over his shoulder.
위협을 느끼면
무너질 겁니다
He'll be wondering who's gonna
come for him next.
여잔 어때?
How's our girl?
자네 차가운 가슴을
녹였나?
Melted your cold heart yet?
콜
Call.
폴드
Fold.
콜
And call.
플레이어 셋
Three players.
30만!
Three hundred grand.
30만 베팅
Bet. Three hundred thousand.
콜
Call.
And call.
플레이어 셋
Three players.
체크
Check.
"본드"씨?
Monsieur Bond?
50만 베팅
Bet. Five hundred thousand.
안절부절 못하는 게
블러핑이 틀림없소
Look. lt's the tell. He is bluffing.
'제임스'가 옳았어
My God, James was right.
결정하시죠
lt's up to you.
100만으로 올립니다
Raise. One million.
기똥찬 패를
가졌나 보군
Seems someone knows
something l don't.
폴드
Fold.
두분 남았습니다
Heads up, gentlemen.
결정하시죠
lt's up to you.
200만!
Two.
200만으로 올립니다
Re-raise. Two million.
결정하세요
And it's up to you.
올인!
l'm all in.
총 천 4백 5십만
Well, it's 1 4 million
and 5OO, OOO.
받으실 겁니까?
lt's up to you, Monsieur Bond.
"본드"도 올인할 거요
Bond will have to go all in
to call his bluff.
콜!
- Call.
카드를 보여주시죠
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
킹과 에이스
풀하우스입니다
Full house. Kings and aces.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
잭 포카드
"르쉬프"씨가 이겼습니다
lt's four jacks.
Monsieur Le Chiffre wins.
블러핑인 줄 알았소?
You must have thought
l was bluffing, Mr. Bond.
Please.
1시간 쉬겠습니다
We will now break for one hour.
기본 베팅액을
20만으로 올립니다
When we return,
the big blind will be 2OO, OOO.
좋은 게임이었소
Good game.
5백만 달러를 줘
계속하겠어
Well, l'm gonna need the other
5 million to buy back in.
그렇겐 못해요
l can't do that, James.
실수한 거야
Look, l made a mistake.
성급하게 덤볐어
이길 수 있어
l was impatient, maybe l was arrogant,
but l can beat him.
- 유감이에요
- 유감?
- l'm sorry.
- Sorry?
유감이라구?
Sorry?
"르쉬프"가 이겨서
Try putting that in a sentence.
딴 돈이
"Sorry Le Chiffre's gonna win...
테러에 쓰일 거라
유감인가?
...continue funding terror and killing. "
That kind of sorry?
지금 그 태도론
절대 못 이겨요
You lost because of your ego,
and that same ego can't take it.
포기해요
That's what this is about.
해봐야 다 잃어요
All you're going to do now
is lose more.
멍청이군
Then you're an idiot.
- 네?
- 멍청하다고!
- l'm sorry?
- l said, you're a bloody idiot.
내 눈을 봐
Look in my eyes .
이길 거란 거 알잖아
l can beat this man, you know that.
팔 놔줘요
Get your hand off my arm.
보드카 마티니
Vodka martini.
- 흔들까요, 저을까요?
- 상관없어
- Shaken or stirred?
- Do l look like l give a damn?
여잘 데리고 나가요!
- James.
- Get the girl out.
재밌는 게임이죠?
Funny game, right?
인사가 늦었소
Sorry, l should've introduced myself,
seeing as we're related.
"펠릭스 라이터"
CIA 소속이요
Felix Leiter, a brother from Langley.
정신만 바짝 차리면
You should have a little faith.
놈을 잡을 수 있어요
lf you keep your head about you,
l think you have him.
그러기엔
너무 늦었소
Had. Excuse me.
계속 할 거죠?
You're not buying in?
아니
No.
지금 같아선 나도
얼마 못 버텨요
Listen, l'm bleeding chips.
l'm not gonna last much longer.
당신을 밀어주겠소
You have a better chance.
l'll stake you.
판돈을 대주겠단 거요
l'm saying l'll give you the money
to keep going.
조건은 하나
놈을 CIA에 넘겨요
J ust one thing. lf you pull it off,
the C lA bring him in.
딴 돈은?
And what about the winnings?
돈엔 관심 없소
Does it look like
we need the money?
베팅액 올릴까요?
Shall we up the blinds?
좋소
Why not?
받겠소
Bet.
올리겠소
Raise.
And fold.
Excuse me, please.
콜
Call.
올리겠소
Raise.
5십만으로 올립니다
Raise. Five hundred thousand.
폴드
- Fold.
- Thank you.
폴드
Fold.
Thank you.
이겼습니다
Wins.
이번엔 빠지겠소
Deal me out.
기본 베팅은
하셔야 돼요
Sorry, sir. You are the big blind.
베팅하세요
Small blind, please.
- 누구야?
- 007!
- Who is it?
- lt's OO7.
"본드"가 심장마비
일으켰어요
Bond's been poisoned.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
침착해
시키는 대로 안 하면
Stay calm and don't interrupt.
Because you'll be dead...
2분도 못 가서 죽어
...within two minutes
unless you do exactly what l tell you.
말해
l'm all ears.
전기충격기 꺼내
Remove the defibrillator
from the pouch.
- 독극물 종류는?
- 확인 중
- Do we know what it is yet?
- We're still scanning.
이제 가슴에 붙여
Attach the leads to your chest.
다량의 강심제야
Ventricular tachycardia. Digitalis.
뭘로 중화시키지?
What do we give him? The kit
has amphetamines, antihistamines...
하이드로코티손, 아드레날린?
...hydrocortisone. Adrenalin?
- 충전 끝나면...
- 리도카인!
- As soon as it reads charged
- Lidocaine. That'll work.
아직 누르지 마
기다려!
Bond, don't push the red button yet.
Do you hear me? Don't push it.
심장이 멈출 거야
His heart's gonna stop.
의식을 잃기 전에
해야 돼
There' s only time for one charge
before he passes out.
주사기를 꺼내서
목 혈관에 찔러
Take the blue combipen, Bond.
Mid-neck into the vein.
강심제 중화제야
That'll counteract the digitalis.
곧 의식을 잃을 텐데
You're going to pass out
in a few seconds.
심장이 멈추면 안돼
You need to keep your heart going.
Push the red button now, Bond.
빨간 버튼 눌러
- 버튼 눌러!
- 눌러!
- Bond, push the damn button !
- Do it now!
- 괜찮소?
- 저요?
- You okay?
- Me?
- 고마워
- 뭘!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- 병원으로 직행해
- 알았어
- Now get yourself off to a hospital.
- l will do.
게임부터 이기고!
As soon as l've won this game.
다시 가려구요?
You're not seriously
going back there?
말이라고!
l wouldn't dream of it.
1백만 베팅
Bet. One million.
- 올인!
- 올인입니다
- All in.
- Call. All in.
카드 보여주세요
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
에이스, 7 투 페어
Two pair. Aces and sevens.
퀸이 이겼습니다
Queen plays. Wins.
미안하군
Oh, l'm sorry.
거의 죽다 살아왔소
That last hand, it nearly killed me.
칩을 바꾸고
마지막 라운드에
Gentlemen, with this chip exchange,
we enter the final phase of the game...
들어갑니다
...which means no more buy-ins.
최소 베팅액은
1백만 달러입니다
The big blind is now
1 million dollars.
플레이어 넷
Four players.
베팅하세요
lt's your bet.
- "본드"씨?
- 체크
- Monsieur Bond?
- Check.
- 체크
- 판돈이 2천 4백만이야
- Check.
- Twenty-four million in the pot already.
체크
Check. And check.
모두 체크
All check.
플레이어 넷
Four players.
체크
- Check.
6백만, 올인!
All in. Six million.
6백만 올인입니다
Bet. Six million. All in.
5백만 올인
Five million. All in.
베팅액은 6백만
Bet is 6 million.
올리겠소
Raise.
올립니다
1천 2백만,
받으실 겁니까?
Twelve million. Heads up.
4천 5십만, 올인!
Forty million, 5OO, OOO. All in.
올인
Raise. All in.
기꺼이 받아주지
Well, l think l will call you
on that one.
콜
Call.
총 판돈이
1억 5천만 불이요
One hundred and fifteen million
in the pot.
카드 보여주시죠
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
에이스, 킹, 퀸
플러시
Flush. Ace, king, queen.
풀하우스
8 석장, 에이스 두장
Full house. Eights full of aces.
더 높은 풀하우스
A higher full house.
에이스 3장, 6 두장
Aces full of sixes.
"본드"씨
Monsieur Bond.
스페이드 5와 7
Five and seven of spades.
스트레이트 플러시
A straight flush.
4부터 8까지
Four to the eight.
더 높습니다
The high hand.
"본드"씨가 이겼습니다
Monsieur Bond wins.
- 팁이요
- 감사합니다
- For you.
- Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
- 놈을 데려가요
- 고맙소
- He's all yours.
- Much appreciated, brother.
축하해요
Congratulations.
축하는 제대로 해야지
You know,
l think a celebration's in order.
좀 살만한가 보네요
You were almost dead an hour ago.
가지, 배고프군
Come on, l'm famished.
Thank you.
"매티스" 말론
CIA가 "르쉬프"를
Mathis says the Americans
have made contact with Le Chiffre.
새벽에 미국으로
데려간대요
They're going to extract him
before dawn.
"베스퍼"로 짓겠어
You know, l think
l'll call that a Vesper.
뒷맛이 씁쓸해서?
Because of the bitter aftertaste?
아니, 한번 맛 들이면
딴 건 못 마시지
No. Because once you've tasted it,
that's all you want to drink.
- 작업 멘트 같소?
- 무척이나!
- l thought that was quite a good line.
- lt was a very good line.
웃고 있잖소
But you're laughing at it.
- 당신만큼은 아니죠
- 그럼 괜찮군
- Not so much it as you.
- Well, that's fine then.
뭔지 알았어
l figured out what that is.
알제리 사랑 매듭
lt's an Algerian love knot.
그래요?
예뻐서 한 건데
Really? l thought it was
just something pretty.
아니
No, you didn't.
누군가 준 거지
Someone gave that to you.
누군지 행운아군
He's a very lucky man.
감정 조절 잘 하죠?
You can switch off so easily,
can't you?
사람 죽이면
죄책감은?
lt doesn't bother you,
killing those people?
그딴 건 안 느껴
Well, l wouldn't be very good
at my job if it did.
못 믿겠어요
l don't believe you.
선택의 문제죠
You've got a choice, you know?
한번 발 들여놨다고
J ust because
you've done something...
계속 하란 법 없어요
...doesn't mean
you have to keep doing it.
충고 받는 건 싫지만
주는 건 괜찮다?
Why is it people who can't take advice
always insist on giving it?
내 앞가림은 해요
You think l can't take
my own advice?
말 못할 고민이
있는 것 같은데
l think something is driving you.
난 영원히 모르겠지
And l think l'll never find out
what that is.
"매티스" 호출이에요
Mathis needs me.
굿나잇
Good night.
축하해요
Congratulations again.
"매티스"!
Mathis.
네놈 친구 "매티스"는
l'm afraid your friend Mathis
is really...
사실 내 친구야
...my friend Mathis.
대단한 근육질이군
You've taken good care
of your body.
죽이기 아까워
Such a waste.
고문하는데
You know...
절대 복잡한 방법 쓸
필요 없어
...l never understood
all these elaborate tortures.
이건 간단하면서도
lt's the simplest thing...
남자한텐 최악의
고통을 안겨주지
...to cause more pain
than a man can possibly endure.
물론
And of course...
육체적 고통보다
더 고통스러운 건
...it's not only the immediate agony,
but the knowledge...
너무 오래 버텼다간
...that if you do not yield
soon enough...
평생 남자 구실
못한단 공포감이야
...there will be little left
to identify you as a man.
묻겠다
The only question remains...
나한테 협조하겠나?
...will you yield in time?
난 돈을 원해
l want the money.
계좌번호는 여자한테
알아낼 테니까
Miss Lynd will give me the account
number, if she hasn't already.
비밀번호만 말해
So all l need from you
is the password.
비밀번호, 뭐야?
The password, please.
아랫도리가
l've got a little itch...
좀 가려운데
...down there.
긁어주겠나?
Would you mind?
아니!
No ! No ! No !
좀 더 오른쪽!
오른쪽!
No. To the right.
To the right. To the right!
개그맨이 따로 없군
You are a funny man, Mr. Bond.
Yeah !
그래, 그래!
Yes, yes, yes.
내 거시길 긁어주다가
죽었다면 다들 웃겠군
Now the whole world's gonna know
that you died scratching my balls.
내가 죽어?
l died?
- 내가 죽어?
- 그래!
- l died?
- Yes.
난 비밀번호를
안 알려줄 거고
Because no matter what you do,
l'm not gonna give you the password.
그럼 네 고객들이
Which means your clients
will hunt you down...
널 산채로
찢어 죽일 테니까
...and cut you into pieces of meat
while you're still breathing.
날 죽였다간
Because if you kill me...
목숨 부지 못해
...there'll be nowhere else to hide.
틀렸어!
But you are so wrong !
네놈과 여잘 죽여도
Because even after l slaughtered
you and your little girlfriend...
네놈 상관들은
날 반겨줄 거야
...your people would still welcome me
with open arms...
내가 아는 정보가
탐날 테니까
...because they need what l know.
착각하지 마
The big picture.
비밀번호를 대면
Give me the password...
여잔 살려주겠다
...and l will at least let her live.
살리고 싶으면
입 열어
Bond. Do it soon enough
and she might even be in one piece.
끝까지 말 않겠다?
You really aren't going to tell me,
are you?
No.
그렇담
So l think...
거시길 잘라서
입에 넣어주지
...l'll feed you
what you seem not to value.
돈을 구할게요
l'll get the money.
돈은 꼭 준다고
전해요
Tell them l'll get the money.
넌 돈보다 중요한
신뢰를 잃었다
Money isn't as valuable to our
organization as knowing who to trust.
Francesco.
"베스퍼"
Vesper.
안 돼
No.
"매티스"는 안 돼
Not him.
Not Mathis.
안 돼
No.
의사 불러올게요
l'll get the doctor.
그는 안 돼
Not him.
이유가 뭘까?
Any ideas?
- 뭐?
- 왜 둘을 살려뒀을까?
- What?
- Why they left the two of you alive.
"베스퍼"는?
Where is she?
자고 있어
Sleeping.
이걸 먹이라고 하더군
Well, l'm supposed
to get you to drink this.
이상하잖아?
lt's just odd...
전부 다 죽이면서
둘만 살려뒀다니
...killing everyone else
but leaving you and her untouched.
우리한테
메시지를 전한 거야
Almost as if someone
was trying to tell us something.
킬러를 봤나?
Get a look at the killer?
아니
No.
유감이군
Shame.
쭉 마셔
Drink up.
기억나는 거 없나?
Anything else you remember?
우리한테 도움될 만한?
Anything that can help us?
"우리한테"?
Help us?
당신이 아니라?
Or help you?
Hello.
괜찮아?
You all right?
잠에서 깨어나
l can't resist waking you.
날 지긋이 바라보는
당신의 눈빛을 보면
Every time l do, you look at me as if
you haven't seen me in years.
다시 태어난
기분이 들어요
lt makes me feel reborn.
다시 태어난 거면
lf you'd just been born...
나체여야 하잖아?
...wouldn't you be naked?
한방 먹었네요
You have me there.
난 당신 여자예요
You can have me anywhere.
진심이야?
l can?
언제 어디서든지!
Yeah. Here, there,
anywhere you like.
내가 좋아졌단
소린가?
Does this mean
that you're warming to me?
Yeah. That's how l would describe it.
네, 그래요
lt's just that not so long ago...
얼마 전까지만 해도
...l would have described
your feelings towards me as....
나같은 인간을...
"혐오"말고 적절한
단어 없을까?
l'm trying to think
of a better word than "loathing"
난 복잡한 여자거든요
l'm afraid l'm a complicated woman.
무서운 여자란 뜻이군
That is something to be afraid of.
- Hello.
- Oh, perfect timing.
하필이면 지금!
'멘델' 씨
스위스는 어때요?
Monsieur Mendel.
How are things in Switzerland?
재촉하긴 싫지만
My apologies,
l do not mean to rush...
워낙 큰돈이라
...but 1 2O million
is a large sum of money.
이해해요
혹시 초콜릿 가져왔소?
lt certainly is. You didn't bring
any chocolates with you?
아뇨
l'm afraid not.
계좌번호 입력하세요
lf you would type in
the account number.
이제 비밀번호
And now the password.
당신이 해
You can do that.
난 모르는걸요
l would if l knew what it was.
V... E-S...
P-E-R
V-E-S-P-E-R.
이체됐습니다
The funds have been transferred.
방해해서 죄송해요
Sorry for disturbing you.
- Auf Wiedersehen.
- Auf Wiedersehen, Herr Mendel.
"제임스"
You know, James...
당신한테 남은 거라곤
...l just want you to know
that if all that was left of you...
그 미소와
손가락뿐이라도
...was your smile
and your little finger...
나한텐 누구보다
남자다울 거예요
...you'd still be more of a man
than anyone l've ever met.
손가락으로 많은 걸
할 수 있단 걸 아니까
That's because you know
what l can do with my little finger.
- 몰라요
- 알고 싶잖아?
- l have no idea.
- But you're aching to find out.
날 들여보내주지
않을 거죠?
You're not going to let me
in there, are you?
굳게 걸어 잠가둔
You've got your armor back on.
당신 가슴속에?
That's that.
닫혀있지 않아
l have no armor left.
당신이 열었지
You've stripped it from me..
내게 남은 것
Whatever is left of me....
내게 남아있는
Whatever is left of me...
모든 것들
...whatever l am....
당신 꺼야
...l'm yours.
M은 좀 바쁠 거야
l suppose M won't miss me
for a couple of days.
"매티스"를 심문하느라
She'll be too busy sweating Mathis.
"매티스"?
Mathis?
"르쉬프"의 블러핑을
알아챈 걸
Remember l told you
about Le Chiffre's tell?
"매티스"가
놈한테 알려줬어
Well, Mathis told Le Chiffre.
그래서 졌던 거지
That's how he wiped me out.
팔에 심었던
칩도 그렇고
Same goes for the implant. Can't say
l'm too sorry about losing that.
믿기질 않아요
l can't believe it.
나도 그래
No, neither could l.
친구로 여겼는데
l thought he had my back.
교훈을 배운 거지
But there you go, lesson learned.
숨기면 티가 나요?
Does everyone have a tell?
그럼
Yes.
전부 다
Everyone.
당신만 빼고!
Everyone except you.
그래서 사랑하지만
l wonder if that's why l love you.
날 사랑해요?
You love me?
당신을 위해 정직한 일
Enough to quit
and float round the world with you...
찾아볼 생각할 만큼
...until one of us
has to find an honest job.
정직한 일이 뭔지는
전혀 감 안 잡히지만
But l think that's gonna have to be you.
l've no idea what an honest job is.
진심이에요?
You're serious.
당신 말처럼
Like you said...
영혼마저 핏빛으로
...you do what l do for too long...
물들기 전에
...and there won't be any soul
left to salvage.
이 일 그만두겠어
l'm leaving with
what little l have left.
그럼 되나?
ls that enough for you?
'M: 은퇴하겠습니다'
'제임스 본드'
- Come on.
- No. No.
그만해요
은행에 가야 돼요
No, stop it. Stop.
l have to get to the bank.
몇 시죠?
What's the time?
한달 여행하는데
얼마나 들까요?
How much do we need
to float for a month?
나한테 돈 있어
l've got plenty.
아뇨, 절반은 내가
낼래요
No, l want to pay for my half
of our aimless wanderings.
목걸이를 뺐군
You stopped wearing the necklace.
네
때가 된 거죠
Yeah. lt was time.
그 남자를 잊을?
Time enough to get over someone?
과거를 잊을 때란 걸!
To realize sometimes
you can forget the past.
당신 상관은
안 그러네요
Though apparently not
your employer.
"1달 후에 돌아가겠음"
Back in one month.
일어나요
돈 찾아올 동안
Come on. l'll get the money...
물건 좀 사와요
...you get supplies.
30분 후에 봐
l'll see you back here
in half an hour.
- M
- 메일 받았네
- Hello, M.
- l got your note.
그래요?
Yes?
그 얘긴 나중에 하고
We'll talk about that later.
지금 재무부에서
손님이 오셨는데
Right now l have a lovely man
from the Treasury here...
딴 돈을
언제쯤 입금할 거지?
...wondering if you're ever
going to deposit the winnings.
이상하군요
받은 줄 알았는데
That's a shame.
l didn't think they'd miss it.
그래, 걱정 말라고
말씀 드렸어
Yes. Well, l told them not to worry.
오늘 입금해
So you'll be depositing it today.
지금 은행에 가죠
On my way to the bank right now.
"멘델"씨 부탁해요
James Bond for Mr. Mendel.
네?
Hello.
돈을 인출하는데
문제가 생겨서요
Mr. Mendel? l'm having trouble
accessing the funds in my account.
지정하신 계좌로
lt was transferred
to the account number...
이체됐는걸요
...your company gave us, Mr. Bond.
지금 인출되는군요
lt appears the funds
are being withdrawn as we speak.
- 어디요?
- 성 마르코 광장
- Where?
- The Venice branch. of course.
베니스 지점
St. Mark's Square.
'게틀러, 30분 후'
무슨 문제라도?
ls there a problem, Mr. Bond?
죽이겠다!
l'll kill her!
내가 죽이지
Allow me.
미안해요, "제임스"
l'm sorry. James.
알제리 계
애인이 있었어
She had a boyfriend.
A F rench Algerian.
무척 사랑했지
They were very much in love.
"르쉬프" 배후조직이
그를 납치하곤
He was kidnapped
by the organization behind Le Chiffre.
협조하지 않으면 죽이겠다며
그녈 협박했지
And they blackmailed her, threatening
to kill him unless she cooperated.
적한테 신경 쓰느라
We should've picked up on it...
정작 내부 단속에는
...but sometimes
we're so focused on our enemies...
신경을 못 썼어
...we forget to watch our friends.
좀 어때?
How are you doing?
휴대폰을 남겼어요
She left her cell phone.
내가 볼 거란 걸
안 거죠
She must have known l'd check it.
자넬 잘 안 거지
She knew you were you.
- "매티스"는 무죄군
- 아뇨
- Well, at least this clears Mathis.
- No.
- 아니라고?
- 네
- No?
- No.
"베스퍼" 혐의만
밝혀진 거죠
We just proved that she's guilty,
not that he's innocent.
계속 캐봐요
lt could've been a double blind.
Keep sweating him.
아무도 안 믿는군
You don't trust anyone,
do you, James?
절대!
No.
교훈을 배웠군
Then you've learnt your lesson.
최대한 빨리 복귀해
Get back as soon as you can..
We need you.
네
Will do.
시간이 필요하면...
lf you do need time....
아뇨
Why should l need more time?
임무 완수했고
그 계집은 죽었어요
The job's done,
and the bitch is dead.
"제임스"...
James...
그날 밤에 어떻게
살아남았는지
...did you ever ask yourself
why you weren't killed that night?
아직도 모르겠어?
lsn't it obvious?
그녀가 거래한 거야
자넬 살리려고
She made a deal to spare your life
in exchange for the money.
살고 싶었겠지만
l'm sure she hoped
they would let her live.
죽을 걸 알았겠지
But she must have known
she was going to her death.
이젠 배후를
밝히긴
And now we'll never know
who was behind this.
불가능해졌어
The trail's gone cold.
"베스퍼 린드"
'제임스에게,
화이트'
- 네?
- "화이트"
- Hello.
- Mr. White?
얘기 좀 하자구
We need to talk.
누구지?
Who is this?
"본드"
The name's Bond.
"제임스 본드"
James Bond.